

ANGELBECERRA

COMPUTER ENGINEER

About me

My experience in the computer field has allowed to acquire specialized skills in software development. I consider myself a proactive, collaborative and results-oriented person.

Languages

Spanish

Advanced

English

Intermediate

German

Basic

Contact

+(58) 424 232 0154

angelfabian.becerra@gmail.com

Portfolio

angelbev.vercel.app

Education

University Alexander von Humboldt University

2020-2023 Computer Engineering.

Udemy FrontEnd Web Developer

2022-2022 University Web Development - FrontEnd Web

Developer. Udemy Certificate of Completion.

Experience

Aquaklin Web Development

2023 - 2023 Design, development and deployment, domain

configuration.

GaleryAn Web Development

2023 - 2023 Web system development, dashboard,

deployment, domain configuration, team

collaboration.

Ferralca Web Development

2022 - 2022 Design, development and deployment, domain

configuration.

Skills

JavaScript	APIs	Flutter
Node.JS	MongoDB	AWS
Express.JS	Front-End	Netlify
React.JS	Back-End	GitHub
Cit	Notion	Figma

Deployment
Responsive Design
UX/UI Design
Version Control
Linux